Tomáš Mikula

UI/UX Game Design

Thanks to my experiences across fields, I see myself as a perspective candidate for UI/UX designer in the game industry.

My skillset includes knowledge of UI design, cognitive psychology, programming, and games (yes, I am a gamer!), and I am used to explaining and communicating design to technical thinkers.



Skills

- · UI/UX Design and visualisation
- Figma/Sketch and similar design related tools
- strong programming skills in Python
- · communication with technically oriented people
- academia experience (teaching, research, etc.)
- · attention to detail

Experience

Dept. of Computer Science - Palacký University 2018 - present

UI/UX design, print design

User interfaces course 2018 - present

Teaching UI/UX course at Palacký university, author of lecture materials.

beecode.io 2016 - present

UI/UX design, external consultations - <u>Unizone</u>, Noc vědců and <u>other projects</u>

Education

Ph.D.	Department of Computer Science, UPOL Relational data and cognitive psychology	2018 - present
MSc	Department of Computer Science, UPOL Master thesis - Award winner of Dean of the Falculty of Science UP	2016 - 2018
BSc	Department of Computer Science, UPOL	2013 - 2016